<Document>
# Alchemy

Alchemy is one of the activities that can be practiced during the expedition.

The main task of alchemy is to produce various substances, from medicines to poisons, by processing, mixing and transforming reagents.

The produced substances, your character as a mercenary, can use for anything. Selling healing potions, smearing weapons with poison, or poisoning your target as an antagonist.

## What you have to work with

A large number of “raw” substances can be found in the world. The juices of plants, the blood of living creatures, or even crushed crystals. A skilled alchemist can transform these, to most people, useless items into something valuable.

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14BloodGrass"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14AgaricMushroom"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14ChromiumSlime"/>
</Box>
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14WildSage"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14QuartzShard"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14LumiMushroom"/>
</Box>


Most of these “raw” ingredients can first be pulverized using a pestle and mortar:

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14Mortar"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14Pestle"/>
</Box>


After putting the raw substances inside the mortar, you need to grind them thoroughly, clicking them frequently with the pestle. Gradually, all the objects will disappear and there will be a liquid left in the mortar, which you can pour wherever you want.

To learn what kind of liquids are in the vessels, you can use special alchemical glasses, available only for the “Alchemist” role.

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14ClothingEyesAlchemyGlasses"/>
</Box>


Also, the following tools can help you in your science:
- Dropper. Allows you to transfer small doses of liquids, from 0.25u to 1u
- Vials of various sizes and strength.
- Small cauldron. Not a bad vessel to heat on an alchemical stove.
- Large Vat. A huge container that can be heated on a campfire. Will help to produce substances on an industrial scale.
- Alchemical furnace. A wood-fueled stove that allows you to heat your solutions.
- Solution Normalizer. A technological device capable of rounding down to the nearest multiple of 0.25u all the reagents poured into it. Helps get rid of tiny interfering residues if something went wrong. Requires an energy crystal to work.

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14Cauldron"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14AlchemyFurnace"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14AlchemyNormalizer"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14BaseVat"/>
</Box>
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14Dropper"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14VialTiny"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14VialSmall"/>
</Box>

## Basic Reagent System

All alchemy is based on the idea of [textlink="Basic Reagents" link="CP14_EN_BasicAlchemy"]. Each basic reagent is a liquid with one strong effect. 

There is also an “Empty Solution”. This is a special basic reagent that has no effects. 

Chances are 50% or more of your potions will be filled with Empty Solution, and that's okay: The balance is built so that even highly diluted base reagents are quite effective.

Given that you [color=red]do not have the ability to separate mixed substances[/color], your job as an alchemist is to find methods of brewing pure potions without impurities, or brewing effective combinations of effects in a single potion.

## Random Reagent Generation

As you study recipes for brewing basic reagents, you may notice a “Random Reagents” box. Each game round, most recipes have unknown additional reagents. In one round, the fly reagents may yield only poison, while in another round they may additionally yield a hallucinogen, or vomit solution.

These additional reagents are stable throughout the round, but it still means you have to find your way to pure solutions each time anew.

## Impurities

Most raw reagents can be boiled down to produce a set of base reagents.
But also, most raw reagents have a second use: impurities.

By interfering a raw, uncooked reagent into a potion of base reagents, you can edit it. For example, by adding chromium slime to a potion, you can invert all of its effects - turning poison into medicine.

</Document>
