<Document>

# Imperial Laws
Publication of the official jurisdictional body of the Zellasian Empire .

## Preamble
This set of laws of the Empire is designed to ensure order, justice and security throughout the territory of the Empire. The laws are mandatory for all citizens, temporary residents and guests of the Empire. Ignoring or violating the provisions set out in this book is punishable in accordance with the established norms.

Every crime recorded on the territory of the Empire is assessed according to the following parameters:

Severity category - determines the basic level of punishment.
Modifiers - increase or decrease responsibility.
Sentence - the final measure of punishment is determined by the authorized body (or designated persons).

## Section I. Categories of Crimes

### Minor violations
Crimes that do not cause significant harm to person or property.

[bold]Examples:[/bold]

1)	Insult to the Empire.

2)	Damage to property or cruelty to animals.

3)	Petty theft (up to 1 silver coin).

4)	Disturbance of public order

[bold]Punishments:[/bold]

1)	Fines, not only material, but also limiting rights and services for a certain period of time

2)	Community service for the benefit of the injured party or the city as a whole

3)	Apology to the injured party.

[bold]One type of punishment is selected without taking into account modifiers.[/bold]


### Mild violations
Actions that affect authorities or cause moderate harm to others.

[bold]Examples:[/bold]

1)	Resistance to government officials.

2)	Negligence in the performance of duties.

3) Failure to pay protection fee and/or licence trade tax.

4)	Steal from 1 silver coin to 1 gold coin.

5)	Causing minor bodily harm.

[bold]Punishments:[/bold]

1)	Fines, not only material, but also limiting rights and services for a certain period of time

2)	Double compensation for damages to the injured party.

3)	Public works for the benefit of the Empire.

[bold]Are selected without taking into account modifiers[/bold]


### Moderate violations
Actions that cause significant harm or threaten the stability of the Empire.

[bold]Examples:[/bold]

1)	Arbitrariness or abuse of authority.

2)	Sabotage.

3)	Robbery (from 1 gold coin).

4)	Causing moderate harm to health.

[bold]Punishments:[/bold]

1)	Double compensation for damages to the injured party.

2)	Expulsion from a faction, camp (both temporary and permanent)

3)	Atonement for punishment through the demiplane to complete the task.

4)	The victim has the right to challenge the accused to a duel. The accused's victory in the duel removes the charges.

[bold]One type of punishment is selected without taking into account modifiers[/bold]


### Serious violations
Crimes with a high level of danger to society and the structures of the Empire.

[bold]Examples:[/bold]

1)	Forced religious conversion.

2)	Membership in criminal groups.

3)	Racketeering is an illegal extortion of money from entrepreneurs by criminal elements, racketeers, carried out through threats and blackmail.

4)	Murder

[bold]Punishments:[/bold]

1)	Double compensation for damages to the injured party.

2)	Expulsion from a faction, camp (both temporary and permanent)

3)	Atonement for punishment through the demiplane to complete the task.

4)	The victim has the right to challenge the accused to a duel. The murderer's victory in the duel removes the charges.

[bold]Two types of punishment are selected without taking into account modifiers[/bold]


### Extremely severe violations
Particularly dangerous acts that threaten the foundations of the Empire.

[bold]Examples:[/bold]

1)	Betrayal of the Crown.

2)	Terrorist act or robbery raid

3)	especially large-scale theft.

4)	Destruction of the body

[bold]Punishments:[/bold]

1)	Public execution.

2)	Payment of a fine by the head of the defendant's faction

3)	Sent to the Imperial City Court

[bold]One type of punishment is selected without taking into account modifiers[/bold]

## Section II. Crime Modifiers
1. Mitigating circumstances
Self-defense: if the crime is committed in defense of life.
Necessity: The action is taken to prevent a greater threat.
Repentance: admission of guilt and cooperation with authorities.
Inexperience (ignorance): If the offender has no previous offenses or does not understand the rules (e.g. new player), the punishment may be replaced by training or a warning. Applies only to minor and minor-moderate offenses
Effect:
The punishment is reduced by one level (for example, an average violation is considered light-average).

2. Aggravating circumstances
Recidivism: repeat commission of a crime.
Cultural aspect: if the crime violates the canons of religion, traditions or laws of a specific race/faction, this is taken into account (for example, desecration of a shrine).
Presence of victims: If the crime resulted in serious injury, death, or destruction of important objects.
Complicity in collusion: group participation in a violation.

Effect:
The punishment in the current category is increased.
3. Extremely aggravating circumstances
Direct assault: If the offender acted openly and threatened others
Wartime: If the crime is committed during a crisis or war, the punishment is more severe.
Cruelty: If the crime is committed with particular cruelty or sophistication
The organizer of the conspiracy: the leader of a criminal group
Effect:
Transferring the crime to the next level of complexity.

## Section III. The Judicial System
The case is being considered:

Representatives of the guards - for minor and moderate crimes.
By the Imperial Court or the commander of the guard - for medium and serious crimes. The commander of the guard also has the right to delegate authority to a trusted person.

When considering a case, government officials have the right to independently choose a punishment consistent with the category of crimes after taking into account all modifiers, and also if the victim of the crime did not use the right to a duel.
Note for players:
This document is designed to provide a fully immersive gaming experience. The laws of the Empire maintain a fair balance between role-playing and mechanics. Violations and penalties are assessed individually, taking into account modifiers and circumstances.

</Document>
