<Document>

  #Locks
  Ever got those pesky thieves rummaging through your property? Well we have a solution for that! Over at BlackLock Incorporation, we have an invention called Locks. They will for sure keep those sticky thieves out of your personal property.

  #Type of Locks
  There are four version of the locks available in the following metals:
  -Copper (3 teeth)
  -Iron (5 teeth)
  -Gold (6 teeth)
  -Mithril (7 teeth)

  #How to obtain
  Now you may be wondering: "Well how am I supposed to obtain these so call locks?"

  There are two ways to obtained your very own lock.

  You can walk on over to the local blacksmith shop and pay a commission fee for them to create one of your choice.

  OR

  If you are well verse in the skills of blacksmithing yourself, you can create one yourself with one metal bar!

  #Editing a Lock
  Now that you got your brand new shiny lock... what now? From a closer inspection, it looks like the lock is set to all 2s. That is a recipe for instant access to those lockpicking hooligans!
  With a handy screwdriver in hand, you can modify the teeth of the locks from 2 to -2.
  Just right-click your lock with the screwdriver in your active hand and hover over the option "Edit Lock" then select which tooth you want to modify.

  #Keys
  Now that your lock is modified to a combination you want to use, We bet you want to go ahead and slap that lock of wonders to a door/chest of your choice in your household. BUT WAIT!! Every lock always comes with a key to at least unlock it.

  Depending on the method used to obtain the lock, you should have received a key from the blacksmith you just commissioned OR crafted yourself a key with one metal bar at the anvil.

  Fun Fact: Keys and Locks cannot be mixed due to the differences of teeth of the key to the lock.(For Example: Copper Lock and Iron Key)

  #Editing Keys
  Lets say that you are a blacksmith yourself and you have created a lock that is already modified and a brand-new key. The key by default is all flat. (Oops! All 2s!)

  In order to modify a key, you would need an item called "Key File" which requires one iron bar to craft it.

  After crafting the key file, you can use it to modify the key by right-clicking the specific key you want to edit, hover over to the option "Modify Key" and start grinding down the teeth to the same combination to the lock.

  DO BE WARNED! THE GRINDING PROCESS IS A ONE WAY TRIP! IF YOU GRIND TOO FAR, YOU WILL NEED TO CREATE ANOTHER KEY TO REDO!

  #Conclusion
  Congratulation! You are now a proud owner of a lock and a key! You can now go ahead and install the lock onto a door, a chest or any other lockable objects that are missing locks. Be sure to keep that key safe and on your person at all time. You can use an item called a "Key Ring" to store your keys. They should be on you whenever arriving to the village... unless some freak accident occurred and the lost of the key ring was the result.

</Document>
