<Document>

# Demiplanes exploring
Demiplanes are one of the main ways for adventurers and the city as a whole to obtain resources.

The main goal of exploration is for adventurers to obtain resources (ore, loot, etc.) and successfully return them back to their world.

As an adventurer, you can sell resources from the demiplane to artisans and other players at your own prices.

## What research and preparation looks like.

There are "keys" in the game world that allow you to temporarily activate a portal to move into a procedurally generated demiplane with enemies and resources. Within the location there will be generated exits from the demiplane that you will have to find on your own.

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14DemiplanRiftCore"/>
</Box>

When you activate the "key" (via the "Z" key or by clicking on the key), a portal is formed, which will teleport up to 4 players and what they are pulling behind them to the demiplane.
Be aware that you may be immediately attacked by opponents who are near you.

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14DemiplaneTimedRadiusPassway"/>
</Box>

After activation, an active gap remains in the real world, which cannot be moved or destroyed, and its animation shows that players are currently in the demiplane.

Once transported, you have unlimited time to explore the demiplane and gather resources. However, lingering without a reason is not recommended.

When you decide to leave the demiplane after finding the portal, you must touch the portal with your free hand to start the transfer. At this point, you may have time to take the object in your hand again or start dragging it to be carried along with you. If there are no living players left in the demiplane, the demiplane and all gaps leading into it are destroyed.

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14BaseShield"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14ModularIronSword"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14ModularIronPickaxe"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14CrystalLampBlueEmpty"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CP14BaseSharpeningStone"/>
</Box>

## Preparing
To prepare for an expedition to the demiplane, you may need the following items:
- Weapons for all members of the group.
- Vials of healing potions or poison for weapons.
- Sharpening stones to sharpen your weapons on the spot.
- Armor for group members.
- Magical items and/or crossbows (with ammunition) for dealing damage remotely.
- A "key" to open the demiplane.
- Extra bags or crates for collecting loot.
- Belt lanterns or magical lighting.
- A supply of water and food for a short break from exploring.

## Cooperation tips
The entire Demiplane is designed for adventurers to (and should) work as a team. Define the basic concepts amongst yourselves:
- Who will engage in melee and ranged combat?
- Who will be responsible for healing and/or storing medicine vials?
- Who will carry the team's cargo (crates or extra bags) to gather resources?
- How will you divide the items you receive amongst yourselves later on?
- Who will be your team leader during critical situations?
- What will you do with dead and injured team members?

</Document>
