<Document>
  #Innkeeping

  The innkeeper is a role that primarily stays within the town. The jobs of an innkeeper include gardening, bartending, and cooking. 

  Within the inn, an innkeeper will have access to three main areas that they will use.

  ##The garden
  The garden, or farm, is an important asset for any chef. A few seedbeds are found here, as well as a well and some basic supplies.
  To begin farming, locate the supply table in the garden. Usually, a crate will hold a variety of seeds while a table will hold farming instruments like a bucket and hoe. Grab a seed variety and use it on the ground to plant it. Wait a while, and then use any sharp tool (such as a sickle or dagger) to harvest the fully grown crop.

  In order to have your crops stay alive for an extended period of time, make sure to water them often. Keeping plants alive can be made easier with the spell “Plant growth” in the vivification tree, which restores the water, nutrients, and health of a plant. 

  If you have filled all your seed beds with crops and still can’t keep up with demand, you can use the hoe to make more. Consider making a seed bag eventually with this if you have plans to expand your farm. 

  ##The cellar
  The cellar is extremely popular among patrons. Within the usual cellar, several barrels can be found which dispense alcohol. Grab a mug, make sure you are drawing from the keg, and profit.

  A cellar will also contain a few tables and torches, as well as a barrel of water. The tables will usually hold spare mugs. Make sure not to serve too much alcohol at once.. except if your esteemed customer is a dwarf.

  ##The kitchen

  Most of an innkeeper's time will be spent in the kitchen. First things first, materials are needed. Chop some wood for planks (or find some), start growing some crops, find your spare food items, and grab your tools. A good chef will recognize the value of a dagger, usually provided to an innkeeper inside their building. Daggers can be used to harvest plants, chop up food into slices, and fend off patrons that have had a bit too much ale.

  Lets begin with cooking something simple: a green salad. First, begin to grow cabbage, pumpkin, and cucumber. Once the crops are ready, bring them into your kitchen. Go to your cooking table and find the recipe for green salad. You may notice that the crops are in sliced form for the recipe, which is attained simply by using your knife to cut them up. Next, you need to find a plate. Usually some spares are around your ovens. Once all ingredients are near the table, you can begin to cook the salad.

  Green salad is easy to make because it does not need to be heated. However, almost all other food dishes require cooking with your furnace. To use the furnace, find some wood planks and deposit them inside of it. Usually 2-3 planks will keep the fire burning long enough to cook an item. Now that there is fuel, ignite the fire with either a “create flame” spell or a flint and steel. Next, place the uncooked item on top of the furnace (place them on top AFTER the flame is lit so they begin to cook!). Take the food off of the stove quickly or else it will burn into inedible ash, which you can try to market to customers, but it won't end well. The “Freeze” spell can stop a furnace from wasting fuel inbetween cooking. 

  ##Customers

  In the kitchen, there is a small ordering window for customers. It is heavily suggested that you make a small menu with paper and a fountain pen containing the dishes you will make and their prices. Prices can be decided by the innkeeper, but most customers will enjoy it if your prices are affordable. Try to attract customers with different services as well, including music enhanced with bardic magic, special deals, or any sort of gimmick you can come up with. 
</Document>
