<Document>

# 0. Do not attempt to circumvent the rules

Accept these rules as they were intended, not as they are written literally. Circumventing the rules and legal loopholes may also be grounds for a ban at the discretion of the administration.

# 1. Do not exploit the game, use cheats or macros

Using bugs, cheats, macros, and exploits to gain an advantage in the game is STRICTLY prohibited. 
If you gain an advantage accidentally, simply report it to AHELP, otherwise it will be a violation of this rule.

# 2. No sexual content

Erotic role play (ERP) and sexual content are strictly prohibited. This includes direct and indirect references to sexual behavior or actions. A small amount of freedom is allowed only in the context of insults.

Romantic relationships are allowed (no further than hugging and kissing), but should not become the focus of attention for you or other participants in the game.

# 3. Do not incite OOC hatred

Statements containing hate speech, insults, and expressions of intolerance towards other players are not permitted.

This applies to OOC communication, not IC character interactions.

- Intentional attempts to humiliate others because of their real or perceived race, gender, gender identity, orientation, etc. are not allowed.
- Words that are closely associated with insults in real life are not allowed.
- The fact that it is acceptable in your region or that you consider it acceptable is NOT a valid reason.

# 4. Griefing

Do not intentionally harm other players with the aim of ruining their gaming experience. Griefing includes any actions that harm the city or players without a valid role-playing reason.

## Self-antagonism

The game implies that not all characters are peaceful and kind, but you cannot behave like an antagonist if your role does not imply it. Self-antagonism includes:
- Sabotaging the work of other players or factions for no reason;
- Intentionally shirking your duties if you are a member of an important faction;
- Helping antagonists without a valid IC motivation;
- Playing "psychos" characters is prohibited.

## Violence against law enforcement

If law enforcement begins to use excessive force against you, you have the right to defend yourself, but you must follow the rules of conflict escalation (see section 5). Make sure that:
- Your behavior does not provoke conflict without reason;
- You use force proportionate to the threat;
- You try to resolve the conflict nonviolently before resorting to violence.

The following is not permitted:
- Preventive violence against security personnel;
- Using conflict as an excuse for griffing;
- Systematic violation of order without clear IC motivation.

If you have a controversial situation, contact the administration.

# 5. Unprovoked killings and unjustified violence

Random killings without a valid reason (Random Deathmatch or RDM for short) are strictly prohibited. Follow the rules of gradual escalation of conflicts if you believe that conflict is inevitable:

The escalation of conflict should follow these stages:
- Verbal: Shouting, insults, threats.
- Harmless: Pushing, stealing easily replaceable items.
- Non-lethal: Inflicting damage that does not reach critical. Immobilization.
- Lethal: Bringing the target to a critical state by any means. Make sure the target is healed and returned to the round.

Additional notes:

- Self-defense is always permitted to the extent necessary to save one's own life. Preemptive attacks/maiming or striking a person who is already helpless is not considered self-defense.
- Minor conflicts and scuffles are permitted, provided that the offended party has valid reasons. If you are offended, you are expected to resolve the conflict without resorting to violence, as far as possible, and to escalate measures as the conflict continues.
- As the defending party, you increase the degree of escalation of the conflict, up to and including the use of violence, while the initiator of the conflict can always respond in kind.
- If the conflict leads to violence and one of the participants loses their capacity to act, the remaining participant must make an effort to help the other if they have no reason to believe that the other was the antagonist.
- After providing assistance, the conflict is considered over; any new conflict with either participant must be escalated again.
- If you are unsure whether escalation is justified in a given conflict, do not hesitate to contact an administrator for help and clarification.

# 6. Use only the server language

The use of languages that do not correspond to the current server configuration is prohibited. If the server is running in Russian, you cannot use English in IC (In Character, in-game roleplay), OOC (Out of Character, player chat in the round), or in character names.

Conversely, if the server is configured in English, the use of Russian is prohibited.

You must have a sufficient command of the language so as not to cause problems in the game and to be able to communicate with the game administrators if necessary.

# 7. Do not engage in metacommunication

Using information that your character could not have obtained to gain an advantage is strictly prohibited. IC and OOC must be kept separate at all times.

- Metacommunication, or communicating with other players through third-party methods (e.g., Discord) to gain an unfair advantage, is strictly prohibited.
- Sharing information about the current round before it ends in OOC, Discord, or other places is prohibited.
- Streaming is permitted as an exception. However, viewing the stream and participating in the round at the same time is prohibited.
- If your character died and you were removed from the round (for example, your entire group died in the demiplane), and then you were allowed to create a new character in the same round, you must completely forget the experience and knowledge of your previous character. The new character does not know who was in their previous team, does not remember the circumstances of their death, and does not possess any information obtained previously.

# 8. Stay in character

Do not go beyond the boundaries of your character's role and the boundaries of the world.
- Do not use words from the real world that do not make sense within the game.
- Do not create characters with silly names (goblins are allowed), celebrity names, or the names of other well-known players.
- Character names must not have vulgar interpretations or contain advertising.

</Document>